[Music]
so
we have been blessed with an early
snowfall this season
while it is uncertain how long it will
stay its message is clear
the snowflakes whisper of a winter yet
to come
and the animals take note and seek to
fill their bellies while there is still
plants and meat in abundance
have you ever heard of the white stag it
is a symbol
that appears in many ancient legends and
is often associated with the pursuit of
wisdom
spiritual fulfillment and consequently
freedom
i've always connected the stag to the
first snowfall
i imagine it as a harbinger of winter
as a child i remember peeping through
the frosted aspen groves
looking for those pearly antlers and
noble white muzzle
certain legends portray the stag as
running from those who are seeking truth
it does not easily let itself be caught
only those who are patient thoughtful
gentle yet courageous
are ever privy to the magic
as a lover of legends and folklore i've
recently felt the need to re-read my
favorite fairy tales and myths
and connect with the stories that once
entranced and astounded my ancestors
there is something about the first snow
that makes me want to go within
and to spend some time reflecting on the
year seeing it for what it is
full of both good and difficult moments
but also
a time that has become part of my
personal history and a collection of
feelings and events that i can learn
from
and may yet make into my own legends and
stories
that will be passed on to those i love
that being said i have no more words to
describe the beauty of what surrounds me
this day
so i will let nature tell you in her own
[Music]
language
uh
[Music]
you